《超感警探》前情提要
Previously on "The Mentalist"...
簡知道血腥約翰是七名疑犯之一
Jane has worked out that Red John is one of seven men.
布萊特·斯特爾斯
蓋爾·伯特侖
雷·哈弗內
但是血腥約翰同樣知道簡名單上的七人
But Red John also knows the seven names on Jane's list.
里德·史密斯
鮑勃·柯克蘭
我會給你七個名字
I'm gonna give you the seven names,
托馬斯·麥卡利斯特
我需要你在他們的手機上
and I need you to put a G.P.S. bug
裝上帶定位的竊聽器
on each of their cell phones.
-裝好了  -好  我們要緊盯著他們
- The wires are up. - Okay. We watch them like hawks.
全天候記錄他們的行蹤
We log everywhere they go 24/7.
我們獲得一條送往你部門的匿名線報
We have an anonymous tip directed to your unit.
一人或多人于西休倫湖5570號遇險
A person or persons in distress at 5570 West Huron.
布雷特·帕特里奇在那
Brett partridge is there.
帕特里奇
Partridge.
老-老虎
T-tiger...
你看到那個錘子沒有
Just that hammer-- you see that up there?
它錘頭上沾的是不是血跡
Is that blood on the hitting side?
有可能  我叫人來取證
Could be. I'll call forensics.
你看到了嗎  他不想去爬梯子
Did you see that? He did not want to go up that ladder.
那個心理醫生不是說過
Didn't the psychiatrist's office say
血腥約翰恐高嗎
that Red John was afraid of heights?
你從哪兒上來的
Wh-where did you come from?
把手給我
Give me your hand.
調查血腥約翰的時候
While investigating Red John,
國土安全局開始懷疑
Homeland Security's begun to suspect
在加州執法部門里存在著一個
the existence of a powerful secret organization
強大的秘密組織
within California law enforcement.
我們想在聯調局里找人合作
We're looking for partners within the F.B.I.
級別較低的  我們確定可以相信的人
Lower level guys that we're sure we can trust.
也就是我了
That's me.
我們應該多談談  上車吧
We should talk some more. Get in the car.
-我有得選嗎  -沒有
- Do I have a choice? - No.
我看錯你了  你不是血腥約翰
I was wrong about you. You're not red john.
你和我一樣在追捕他
You're hunting him, same as me.
我們都想要報仇
We both want our revenge,
但只有一個人可以做到
and only one of us is going to get it.
-請告訴我嫌犯都有誰  -不行
- Please tell me who the suspects are. - No.
你知道我會拷問你的吧
You understand I'm gonna have to torture you.
把手舉起來  簡  你沒事吧
Put your hands in the air! Jane, you all right?
你會堅持下去吧
Are you gonna finish this thing?
會的
Yes.
執法部門內部確實存在一個強大的組織
There is a powerful organization within law enforcement.
不過比你以為的更大
It's a lot bigger than you thought.
不光是高層參與了
It's not just the big boys, either.
像我這種級別低的也可以進
They even let lower level guys like me in.
柯克蘭探員意圖逃跑
Agent Kirkland tried to escape.
你別無他法  只能將其擊斃
You had no choice but to use deadly force.
明白了嗎
Do you understand?
老虎老虎
Tiger tiger.
加州  舊金山
請先別關電梯門
Hold the elevator.
爸爸  我們能去坐空中纜車嗎
So, dad, can we ride on the cable car?
當然了
Yeah, you bet.
那能去唐人街吃午飯嗎
Then lunch in chinatown?
又去嗎
Again?
我喜歡那里的面條和餃子
I like those noodles, and the dumplings.
你這人怎么回事
Whoa! What the heck?!
你以為你誰啊  不能隨便推我小孩
Hey, how do you think you are? You can't shove my kid.
別想逃  喂  叫你呢
Don't run away from me! Hey! Hey!
給我開門
You open this door!
我要去找管理投訴  聽見沒
I'm complaining to the management! You hear me?
你沒事吧  小家伙
You all right, buddy?
他弄疼你了嗎
He get ya? Huh?
帕克曼先生
Mr. Parkman?
先生  我是酒店保安
Sir, this is hotel security.
帕克曼先生  請你開門
Mr. Parkman, I'm gonna have to ask you to open the door, please.
帕克曼先生  先生
Mr. Parkman? Sir?
我進來了
I'm coming in.
救命
Help.
他捅了我
He stabbed me.
誰捅了你
Who stabbed you?
帕克曼先生
Mr. Parkman?
天啊  帕克曼先生
Oh, jeez. Mr. Parkman?
去找人來幫忙
G-get some help.
快報警  815房間出事了
Uh, call 9-1-1. Room 8-1-5.
死者為白人男性
Deceased white male.
你看到死者表現很焦慮嗎
And you say the victim appeared worried?
是的  他在電梯里
Yeah, he was looking over his shoulder
看起來小心翼翼的  像是有人在追他
when he got in the elevator, like he was being chased.
對  他手里的紙袋里有東西
Yeah. He had something in a paper bag.
好的  當時大概是什么時間
Yeah. And what sort of time was this?
10點55分
10:55.
我在晚上10點58分進了客房
I entered the room at 10:58 P.M.
死者  查德·帕克曼
The victim, Chad Parkman,
痛苦地倒在地上
was on the floor in some distress.
他說他被別人捅傷了
He stated he had been stabbed by another individual.
然而當時房間里好像就他一個人
Although he appeared to be alone in the room.
里斯本  這是酒店的保安隊長
Lisbon. Uh, this is the head of hotel security.
他是知情者  這位是加調局的里斯本探員
A fount of information. Agent Lisbon from the CBI.
她會聽你的敘述
She'll be happy to listen to you.
發現兇器了嗎
Do we have a murder weapon?
沒有  長官  也沒有發現任何
Uh, no, ma'am, nor have I been able to establish
兇手逃跑的出口
any means of egress used by the killer.
那有發現紙袋嗎
Uh, what about a paper bag?
外面那個小孩提到一個紙袋
The kid outside mentioned a paper bag.
廁所里有碎紙片
Uh, just scraps on the toilet.
肯定是撕碎沖進馬桶了
Must have been shredded and flushed.
知道里面裝過什么嗎
Any idea what was in it?
不知道
No idea.
可能是被兇手拿走了
Maybe the perp who killed him took it.
頭兒  剛從警用電臺接到消息
Hey, boss. Just got a call on the radio.
附近又發生一起命案
Another homicide nearby.
好像是因為試圖劫車未遂
Attempted carjacking, looks like.
跟此案有關嗎
Related?
應該沒關系  我覺得還是該去確認一下
Probably not. Thought I'd check it out.
好  查完盡快回來
All right. Come back as quick as you can.
好的
Okay.
我在門外聽到了打斗聲
When I was outside the room, I heard them struggling,
然后聽到了死者被捅時的驚呼
then heard the victim cry out when he was stabbed.
但緊接著我開門進去
But then I got the door open...
屋里只有他一個人
he was all alone.
窗戶開著
Window's open.
這里要到樓下還很遠  到屋頂也是
It's a long way down, and a long way up to the roof.
我覺得他不是從窗戶逃走的
I don't think he went that way.
-那他怎么逃跑的  變魔術嗎  -不
- So, what? Magic? - Nope.
只是個小把戲
Just a trick.
而我們都知道你很擅長這個  不是嗎
And we all know how good you are at those, don't we?
我是說耍小把戲
Tricks, I mean.
-特蕾莎  -雷
- Hey, Teresa. - Ray.
你來這干什么
What are you doing here?
你已經不在加調局工作了
You don't work at the CBI anymore.
-我是跟客戶過來的  -他為天眼組織工作
- I'm with a client. - He works for Visualize.
是的  這事關乎天眼組織
He does, and this is a Visualize matter.
-他們是誰  -這位是杰森·庫珀
- Who are they? - Uh, this is Jason Cooper,
他是邪教頭目布萊特·斯特爾斯的走狗
Errand boy for cult leader Bret Stiles,
還有這位是雷·哈弗內  是邪教組織的成員
and Ray Haffner, who is a member of the cult.
"天眼"不是邪教
Visualize is not a cult,
正是由于這種偏見
And it is exactly bigotry like that
才會導致這樣的命案
that leads to murders like this.
這話是什么意思
What are you talking about?
查德·帕克曼是"天眼"團體中的
Chad Parkman was a prominent member
一個重要成員
of the Visualize community.
我們認為這起命案是由仇恨引發的
We view his murder as a hate crime.
哈弗內先生將會參與你們的調查
Mr. Haffner is to be included in your investigation.
只是單純以死者所在這方的身份
Purely as a victim's advocate,
但能再和你一起工作我的確很開心  特蕾莎
But I do like the idea of working with you again, Teresa.
多謝你的有心  庫伯先生
I appreciate your concern, Mr. Cooper,
但是我們沒有公民參與案件調查的先例  從沒有過
But we never let civilians in our investigations--ever.
從沒有過嗎
Never ever?
-他  他不一樣  -我不一樣
- Well, he's-- he's different. - I'm different.
這里有封副州長簽署的信件
I have a letter here signed by the Lieutenant Governor
邀請哈弗內先生參與案件調查
inviting Mr. Haffner to join the investigation.
只是在一旁觀看進展
To observe. That's all.
讀讀信吧  里斯本探員
Read the letter, Agent Lisbon.
我相信你會同意
I am confident you'll want to grant
執行副州長的要求
the Lieutenant Governor's request.
案子有頭緒了嗎
So... any ideas on the case yet?
只有未解之謎
Just questions.
是個難題  對吧
It's a stumper, isn't it?
說到這個  血腥約翰的案子調查得怎么樣
Speaking of which, how's your Red John investigation going?
勝券在握
In the bag.
我們天眼組織現在在研究你
You know, we study you in Visualize now.
你盲目地跟命運做斗爭
Your blind struggle against fate.
很英勇  也很徒勞
So heroic. So fruitless.
布萊特說從派翠克·簡身上能學到很多
Bret says there's a lot to be learned from watching Patrick Jane,
所以  我們都在研究你
so... we all do.
火氣太大
So much anger.
對你沒好處
It's not good for you.
火氣  我沒有生氣
Anger? I'm not angry.
惡狠狠的狂怒
Annihilating rage.
至于你在氣什么  我不清楚
About what, I have no idea.
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
我能看到你臉上表現出來的
Just what's written on your face.
你比別人都聰明很多  是吧
You're so much smarter than everybody else, right?
但是這并沒有幫你抓住血腥約翰  不是嗎
But it isn't helping you catch Red John, is it?
我們來互換下角色吧
Here's a switch for you.
我給你預測一下未來
I'm gonna predict your future.
有報應在等著你
There's a comeuppance headed your way.
你當靈媒比你當警察還要糟
You're a worse psychic than you were a cop.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
■
翻譯：灰灰是菇涼  Michael  王小麥 木頭  那時花開  愛卿遛小鳥
超感警探
第六季
第五集
■
時間軸：Sagelibra  兜兜兜爹   校對：灰灰是菇涼
第六季
第五集
■
特效&后期：灰灰是菇涼   總監：灰灰是菇涼
案子的死者  查德·帕克曼
So our victim-- Chad Parkman--
生前是一名很成功的奧運會體操教練
was a successful Olympic gymnastics coach.
他在馬林郡[位于加州]有訓練室
He had a facility out in Marin.
他去酒店做什么
What was he doing at he hotel?
體育保健會議  他是主講嘉賓
Sports health conference. He was the keynote speaker.
天眼組織這條線呢
What about the Visualize angle?
有什么發現嗎
Did you find anything there?
沒有證據表明他是天眼組織的成員
Nothing I.D.ing him as a member.
你覺得庫伯在說謊嗎
You think Cooper's lying?
不知道
I don't know.
布萊特·斯特爾斯把他的副手和
Uh, if Bret Stiles sends his second-in-command
私人保安都派來了
and private security,
說明這事對天眼組織很重要
it's important to Visualize somehow.
我們還是友好點吧  我去跟庫伯和解一下
Let's play nice. I'll go make up with Cooper.
你跟哈弗內看一遍監視錄像帶
I want you to go through the security tapes with Haffner.
他喜歡你
He likes you.
多幫幫他  通融點
Just be helpful and accommodating.
讓他多說話
Get him talking.
盡量從他嘴里多套點消息
Pump him for every bit of information that you can.
好的  頭兒  我知道該怎么做
Sure, boss. I know what to do.
但是要小心  你明白的
But be careful. You know.
好的
Yeah.
想跟我去找庫伯談談嗎
Hey. You wanna come with me to talk to Cooper?
不想
Nope.
不能打草驚蛇
We don't want to spook him.
我跟周一起去帕克曼的體操館
I'll take Cho to Parkman's gym.
他可以跟人談談推舉和彎舉
He can talk reps and curls,
而我可以在那四處轉轉
and I'll take a little look around.
好吧  要是我有什么發現再打給你
All right. I'll call you if I find anything out.
加州  馬林郡  帕克曼的體操館
好的  現在
All right, now...
落地要穩  吉米
Stick the landing, Kimmy.
好的
Good...
太好了
Gah! That's right!
她可真厲害
Wow. She's impressive.
2016年里約奧運會  那是她的目標
You know, Rio 2016-- that's the goal.
帕克曼是首選教練嗎
And, uh, Parkman was your first choice as coach?
當然了  帕克曼提出要訓練你的孩子嗎
You bet. Uh... Parkman offering to coach your kid?
他可能要忙吉米這邊
Ah, you know, he's probably too busy with kimmy
沒空管你的孩子了  不過他是最好的
to take your kid on, but, uh, he's the best.
是嗎
Yeah?
吉米在他指導下更加刻苦訓練  而我卻做不到
He got Kimmy to bear down in ways I never could.
她以前經常跟朋友發短信
She's always texting with friends,
周五晚上經常跟男孩們去吃披薩
wanting to go for pizzas on a Friday night with boys.
現在都改了
No more of that.
真是謝天謝地
Thank goodness.
而且我從不擔心
And I never felt I have to worry
她和教練單獨在一起
about her being alone with him.
這很重要  是吧
Well, that would be important, wouldn't it?
謝了
Thanks.
帕克曼先生談過他的私生活嗎
Did Mr. Parkman ever talk about his personal life?
沒有  從來沒有  有時出于禮貌
No, never. I would ask questions sometimes
我會問點這方面問題  但他回答都很含糊
just to be polite, you know, and he would just be very vague.
謝謝你
Thank you.
打擾一下
Uh, excuse me--ooh!
小心點
Whoa, careful.
-你沒事吧  -沒事
- You all right? - Yeah.
看來我不應該穿高跟鞋
Guess I shouldn't have worn heels.
我妹妹對體操挺感興趣的
Um, my little sister's interested in gymnastics.
你能給我介紹一下這些價格嗎
Could you help explain this pricing to me?
我不是這里的員工
Uh, I don't work here.
-我  -抱歉  你是加調局的嗎
- Oh. I-- - Excuse me. You're the guy from CBI?
是的  我是周金寶探員
That's right. Agent Kimball Cho.
我是比爾·麥勒  體操館的共同所有人
I'm Bill Mylar, co-owner.
-我們通過電話  -是的
- We talked on the phone. - Right.
等一下  你是來調查什么的嗎
Oh, wait. You're here investigating something?
謀殺案
A murder.
我以為你們會直接去我辦公室
I thought you were gonna come directly to my office.
我們想跟你們的客戶談談
Uh, we decided to talk to come of your clientele.
你不會介意的  是吧
You don't mind, do you?
只要能幫上忙就行  事實是
Anything that helps, but the truth is,
這個體操館里的所有人都喜歡查德
everybody here at the gym loved Chad.
對死去的人大家都會這么說
People always say that about the dead.
但很少是真心話
Seldom is it true.
有什么地方我們能單獨談談嗎
Is there someplace private we can talk?
這么說  你是個警察
So... you're a policeman.
很抱歉  剛才我太丟人了
I'm so sorry. I'm embarrassed.
-有人死了嗎  -是的
- Somebody died? - Yes.
我的天  謀殺案
Oh, my gosh, a murder?
你認識查德·帕克曼嗎
Did you know Chad Parkman?
這家體操館的老板嗎
The gym owner?
不認識  發生什么了
No. What happened?
那里有一個體操館的職員
There's a staff member right over there.
他們會給你介紹價格的事
They can tell you about the pricing.
硬漢  是吧
Tough guy, huh?
謝了
Thanks.
請問一下
Excuse me.
很抱歉剛才我們給了你不好的印象
I'm sorry we got off on the wrong foot.
現在我向你保證我會全力
Now I want you to know that I am completely committed
追查殺害帕克曼先生的兇手
to finding whoever killed Mr. Parkman.
我們的目標是一致的
Our interests are the same.
鑒于此  不知你能不能告訴我一些
In light of that, I-I was wondering if you could give me
有關帕克曼先生以前在天眼組織的情況
a little history as to Mr. Parkman's role in Visualize.
我沒有找到任何證據
I haven't been able to find any evidence
表明他跟天眼組織有關
linking him to the organization.
查德是在最近才對真相有所認知
Chad's eyes were opened to the truth only recently.
但他非常虔誠
But he was deeply committed.
我們想重用他
We had big plans for him.
怎么重用
What kind of plans?
查德·帕克曼在所有人心目中
Chad Parkman had very positive name recognition
都有很好的聲譽
across all quadrants.
人們最經常用來形容他的一個詞
The most commonly used word to describe him
就是"值得信賴"
was "Trustworthy."
所以你們想讓他來做公共外聯嗎
So you were gonna use him for public outreach?
是的  差不多吧
Something like that, yes.
你覺得這是他被害的原因嗎
Do you think that's why someone killed him?
很有可能
It's a strong possibility.
帕克曼先生跟布萊特·斯特爾斯的關系怎樣
Uh, what was Mr. Parkman's relationship with Bret Stiles?
對查德來說布萊特·斯特爾斯是他的指路明燈
Bret Stiles was a guide and a beacon for Chad,
對我們來說也是這樣
as he is for all of us.
那斯特爾斯先生在哪里
And where is Mr. Stiles?
我不確定
I can't be certain.
是嗎  你不知道他在哪
Really? You have no idea where he is?
我不需要知道他在物理空間中的什么地方
It is not necessary for me to know where he is in physical space.
如果他需要我  他會找到我的
If he needs me, he will find me.
失陪一下
Would you excuse me?
喂  瑞斯比
Hey, Rigs.
我在劫車案的現場
Hey. I'm at the carjacking scene.
死者中槍了
So the victim here got shot.
在旁邊的座位上我們找到了一把帶血的刀
On the seat next to him, we have a bloody knife.
你覺得和殺死帕克曼的刀是同一把嗎
Do you think it's the same knife that was used to kill Parkman?
是的  有可能
Yeah, it could be.
從這里能看到那家酒店
You can see the hotel from here.
把那把刀送到實驗室
Get that knife to the lab.
-好的  頭兒  -我現在就回加調局
- Will do, boss. - I'm on my way back to CBI.
好的
Okay.
帕克曼是這生意的招牌
Parkman was the face of the business.
我負責具體生意
I do the business.
那你們的生意怎么樣
And how is business?
非常好  我們本來打算在東南部
Phenomenal. We're planning on expanding
東北部  各個地方都開分館
to the southeast, northeast, every place.
現在我不知道該怎么辦了
Now I don't know what we're gonna do.
帕克曼的死也有一定的好處
Well, there are upsides to Parkman's death,
實話實說
Let's be honest.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你這么說就太不人道了
You know, that's a very sick thing to say.
想想那些同情他的新聞報道
Well, think about all the sympathetic press coverage.
這可是免費的廣告啊
That's free publicity right there.
而且有關天眼組織的爛事也沒有了
Plus the whole Visualize mess goes away.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你聽說過天眼組織  對吧
Well, you've heard of Visualize, right?
我當然聽過  就是那個瘋狂的邪教
Of course I have. It's that wacko cult.
跟這又有什么關系
What does that have to do with anything?
帕克曼是天眼組織的一員
Yeah, well, Parkman was a member of Visualize.
-你不知道嗎  -不知道
- You didn't know that? - No.
-你確定  -當然
- You sure? - Yes, I'm sure.
告訴我  查德有經常談論天眼組織嗎
Tell me, did Chad talk about Visualize a lot?
當然  他是那組織的成員
Yeah, sure. Uh... he was a member.
某個詭異的自助小組
Some kind of weird self-help group.
我對那沒興趣  但是如果這能幫他成為好教練
It's not my thing, but if it helped him coach,
那就隨他去吧
all the power to him.
麥勒先生
Mm. And, uh, Mr. Mylar--
他對天眼組織的態度如何
How did he feel about Visualize?
麥勒恨死那玩意了
Oh, Mylar hated that stuff.
他們經常為這吵架
You'd see them arguing about it all the time.
是嗎  他很恨它
Oh, really? Hated it, did he?
被你抓到了  那是個愚蠢的謊言
You got me. A foolish lie.
事實是  我非常憎恨天眼組織
The truth--I was mad as hell about Visualize.
我正在想辦法擴張生意
I'm trying to expand our business,
他卻跑去參加那個見了鬼的邪教
he joins some moonbat cult?
我們經常為此爭吵  我很內疚
We fought about it a lot, so now I feel guilty
我們的關系鬧到那么差
that we ended on bad terms.
但是我可沒殺他
But I didn't kill him.
你確實沒  是嗎
You didn't, did you?
頭兒叫我們回去
Boss wants us back.
里斯本  你查到什么了嗎
Lisbon, you find something?
殺死帕克曼的那把刀
The knife that killed Parkman
出現在了瑞斯比辦的劫車案現場
at the site of Rigsby's carjacking.
被劫對象叫什么
Uh, what was the carjacking victim's name?
弗羅斯特  戴文·弗羅斯特
Frost. Devin frost.
說說戴文·弗羅斯特
Tell me about Devin Frost.
戴文  他原先在這里工作  一個好孩子
Devin? He used to work here. He's a good kid.
真是有趣  案情變復雜了
Interesting news. The plot thickens.
案情變復雜了
Plot thickens.
里斯本
Lisbon?
她掛斷了
She's gone.
我們在酒店一條街外的巷子里
We are in the alley about a block away from the hotel.
找到槍了
We found the gun.
是殺死弗羅斯特的那把槍嗎
Is the gun used to shoot Frost?
看起來是的  槍管上還有接消音器用的膠布
Yeah, looks like it. And there's duct tape on the barrel. For the silencer.
送去做彈道分析  確定是這把槍
Well, get it to ballistics. Make sure it's a match.
看看能不能在上面找到指紋
See if we can get any fingerprints.
好的  掛了
Will do. Bye.
-我們可能找到槍了  -是嗎
- Looks like we've got the gun. - Yeah?
正在送去鑒證科  但是應該沒錯
It's on its way to forensics now, but it's a pretty sure bet.
等哈弗內來了  我們就可以開始了
Well, as soon as Haffner gets here, we'll get started.
我不喜歡現在這情況  頭兒
I don't like it, boss.
哈弗內就不應該來這兒
Uh... Haffner shouldn't even be in our offices.
他是簡的血腥約翰嫌疑人之一
He's one of Jane's Red John suspects.
他還是天眼組織的一員
And he's a member of Visualize.
而這個組織又是另外一個嫌疑人操控的
Which is run by another Red John suspect.
我們應該調查他
We should be investigating him,
而不是讓他參與我們的調查
not letting him join our investigation.
這不是我們能決定的
We don't really have a choice.
就只能這么著了  哈弗內
Might as well make the most of it. Haffner!
特蕾莎
Teresa.
還是一樣美麗
Lovely as always.
伙計們  現在都掌握些什么了
Guys. So what have we got so far?
那就開始吧
Well, let's see.
帕克曼10點48分進入了酒店
Parkman entered the hotel at 10:48.
他很不安  目擊證人認為
He was anxious, and witnesses got the impression
有人在追他
that he was being pursued.
他在電梯里和人發生了口角
He has an altercation in the elevator,
然后大約于10點51分逃進了房間
and Parkman flees to his room at approximately 10:51.
10點58分酒店保安進入了他的房間
And at 10:58, hotel security opened Parkman's room
發現他被人捅傷  奄奄一息地躺在地上
to find him dying on the floor with a stab wound.
11點12分  警察和急救人員趕到
At 12 past 11:00, police and E.M.Ts arrive,
但是他們宣布帕克曼已當場死亡
but they pronounce Parkman dead at the scene.
在那個時間段  沒人能出入那個房間
Nobody could have entered or left the room
而不被人看見
during that time period without being seen.
這邊有個公園
Here's the park.
酒店在一邊
The hotel's on the one side,
而戴文·弗羅斯特是在這里被謀殺的
and this is where Devin Frost was murdered--
在公園的另一邊
On the other side of the park.
弗羅斯特的車里有一把刀
Now, in Frost's car, there's a knife
刀刃上有帕克曼的血跡
with Parkman's blood on the blade
刀把上有弗羅斯特的指紋
and Frost's fingerprints on the handle.
我們還在車里發現了自制消音器
We also found a homemade silencer in the car.
我們在這兒的巷子里發現了和消音器配套的槍
And we found the gun that belongs to the silencer here in the alley,
而從時間上來說  這是做不到的
which, given the timeline, seems to be a physical impossibility.
所以弗羅斯特捅死了帕克曼
So... Frost stabbed Parkman
不知通過何種方式離開了酒店沒被人發現
and somehow left the hotel without being seen,
然后某個不明襲擊者又殺了弗羅斯特
and then an unknown assailant killed Frost?
看起來是這樣
It would look that way.
消音器應該不怎么好使
The silencer didn't work too well.
我們有三個證人在10點57分左右
We have three witnesses who heard a gunshot
聽到了槍聲
around 10:57.
也就是說  弗羅斯特在車里
So, Frost got shot
被射殺的時間
in his car at almost the exact same time
和他應該在酒店捅死帕克曼的時間一樣
that he was supposedly in the hotel stabbing Parkman?
而這是不可能的
Which is impossible.
沒錯
Correct.
所以  你們現在在找的嫌疑人
So, you're looking for an unknown suspect
要么是個魔術師  要么很有可能
who is a magician or quite possibly a wizard
是個巫師
of some kind.
干得不錯  伙計們
Great work, guys.
我們把體操館老板麥勒帶來問話了
Uh, we've brought in Mylar, the owner of the gym.
我們希望他能告訴我們點有用的情況
We're hoping he can shed some light on this,
或者至少給我們一個合理動機
or at least give us a plausible motive.
好吧
Okay then.
我很高興由"最好的"隊伍辦這個案子
Well, I'm so glad we got the "A" Team working this case.
我先回酒店  把線索再過一遍
I'm gonna go back to the hotel and look things over again.
回見
Ciao, kids.
簡說別給麥勒太大壓力
Jane said not to lean on Mylar too hard.
只要問問他帕克曼和弗羅斯特
Just ask him about Parkman and Frost
-看他有什么反應  -好的
- and see how he reacts. - You got it.
抱歉打斷下
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
我桌上有份奇怪的報告
Weird report just came over my desk.
-是關于鮑勃·柯克蘭的  -什么
- It's about Bob Kirkland. - What,
我們逮捕的那個精神變態的國土安全局探員
the psychotic Homeland Security agent we arrested?
是的  他死了
Yeah. He's dead.
死了  怎么會的
Dead? How'd he die?
報告里說  他試圖越獄時
The report says he was killed
-被擊斃了  -當真嗎
- attempting to escape from prison. - Seriously?
-聽起來不太對  不是嗎  -確實不太對
- Doesn't sound right, does it? - No, it doesn't.
我該去查一下
I should check it out, right?
去查查看發生了什么  怎么會發生的
Find out what happened and why.
好的  頭兒
Will do, boss.
-看看從麥勒那里能問出什么  -好的
- And see what we can get from Mylar. - You got it.
戴文·弗羅斯特在體操館工作了多久
How long had Devin Frost worked for you at the gym?
有幾年吧
Couple years.
他和查德·帕克曼關系如何
What was his relationship with Chad Parkman?
帕克曼教過他
Parkman had coached him
并把他培養成助教
and brought him on as an assistant.
弗羅斯特是天眼組織的一員嗎
Was Frost a member of Visualize?
他嗎  我覺得不是
Him? I don't think so.
這些天眼組織的瘋子都有一個共同點
One thing about those Visualize nuts--
他們都很有職業道德
They got a work ethic.
弗羅斯特沒有嗎
And Frost not so much?
所以你才開除他的嗎
Is that why you fired him?
我沒有開除他  他自己辭的職
I didn't. He quit.
是嗎  什么時候
Really? When?
大約一個月之前
About a month ago.
帕克曼去歐洲參加一個體操錦標賽
Parkman went to a gymnastics tournament in Europe.
以前  弗羅斯特都會跟他一起去的
In the past, Frost went with him.
這一次他沒去
This time, he didn't.
相反  他來找我說他要辭職  然后就走了
Instead he walked in, told me he was quitting, walked out.
這是我最后一次見到他
Last time I saw him.
他和帕克曼有過爭執嗎
He and Parkman get into a fight?
沒有  我只是以為他找到了更好的工作
No, uh... I just figured he got a better offer somewhere else
想趁帕克曼不在的時候
and was taking advantage
直接跟我辭職
of Parkman not being around to quit to me.
-他為什么要這么做  -我說過  弗羅斯特少年時
- Why would he do that? - Like I said, Parkman had been
帕克曼就是他的導師了
Frost's mentor since he was a teenager.
我想他沒勇氣
I don't think he had the courage
直接跟帕克曼辭職
to quit to Parkman's face.
你覺得麥勒是兇手嗎
You think Mylar is our killer?
我也不覺得
Me, neither.
庫伯對斯特爾斯的下落
Cooper was awfully cagey with you
守口如瓶  是嗎
about Stiles' whereabouts, wasn't he?
和庫伯談過后  我做了點調查
Mm-hmm. After I spoke to Cooper, I did some digging.
斯特爾斯失蹤了  沒人知道他在哪兒
Stiles is missing. Nobody knows where he is.
是嗎  什么時候
Really? When?
和血腥約翰把勞拉蕾·馬丁斯的錄像帶
Around the same time Red John sent you
寄給你的時間差不多
the Lorelei Martins tape.
頭兒  剛拿到弗羅斯特的通話記錄  看看這個
Boss? I just got Frost's phone records. Look at this.
這是雷·哈弗內的手機號
That's Ray Haffner's cell phone.
弗羅斯特捅死帕克曼一周前
Frost called it three times
給這個號碼打了三次電話
the week before he stabbed Parkman.
我們去看看
Well, let's go to see
雷對此有什么要說的
what brother Ray has to say about that.
他不在那兒  他去酒店了
He's not here. He went to the hotel.
他說他有些事得去調查一下
He said he had to check on something.
那我們就去酒店
Then we'll go there.
不行  你呆在這兒  格蕾絲和我去
No, you stay here. Grace and I will go.
-別傻了  -我們沒問題的
- Don't be ridiculous. - We'll be fine.
相比你去  我們應該能更容易
He's more likely to let something slip to us
從他那兒套出點話來
than he would to you.
好吧  可是我留下干嘛
All right. But what am I supposed to do,
閑坐著嗎
just sit around?
我們到現在還不知道
Well, we still haven't figured out
弗羅斯特捅了帕克曼后是怎么逃離酒店的
how Frost got out of the hotel room after he stabbed Parkman.
除非弗羅斯特壓根就沒去過那兒  對吧
Except Frost couldn't have been there in the first place, could he?
你說那是兇手耍的把戲
You said it was a trick.
那就把它弄明白
Figure it out.
我找到薩城警局
I got the name of the Sac P.D. detective
負責調查柯克蘭被擊斃案的警探了
who investigated Kirkland's shooting.
-他會來一趟加調局  -干得好
- He's gonna come by CBI. - Good work.
老樣子  謝謝
Hey, man. Usual, please.
你要點什么嗎
You want anything?
黑咖啡
Yeah, coffee. Black.
這是個水果攤  周  只有水果
It's a fruit stand, Cho. They sell fruit.
那好  我什么都不要
Okay. No.
再給我來一份全料的  加酸橙和紅番椒
Give me another one with everything -- lime, chili.
謝謝
Thank you.
好的
That's great.
不用找了
Keep the change.
餓死了
I'm starving.
大概是因為剛結婚
I guess you burn a lot of calories,
體力消耗過大吧
being a newlywed.
我沒興趣跟你談這些
We're not having this conversation.
太奇妙了
It's amazing.
本以為婚姻只會讓一切歸于平淡
You'd think that marriage would just cool things off,
可對我們來說  恰恰相反
but for us, it's just the opposite.
別說了  行嗎
Please stop talking.
你知道嗎  現在是我一生最幸福的時刻
You know, I think I'm the happiest I've ever been.
每天早上在她身邊醒來
Every morning when I wake up next to her,
每天晚上一起躺在床上
and every night when we go to bed together,
我就會想  我是世上最幸運的男人
I just think, "Wow, I'm the luckiest man in the world."
你懂的
You know?
我沒胃口了
I just lost my appetite.
所以我要謝謝你
So I wanna say thank you,
因為是你要我把握機會  勇敢面對的
because you were the one that made me take the risk.
我已經開始后悔了
And I'm starting to regret it.
你是好哥們  我欠你份人情
No. You're a good friend, and I owe you.
我也要幫你找到愛人
I'm gonna find you somebody to love.
-不  不用了  -要的  必須的
-No. You're not. - Yes, I am.
相信我  孤獨終老絕不是樁好事
Trust me, there is no point in going through life alone.
你真的不想吃了嗎
Are you really not gonna eat that?
謝謝
Thanks.
特蕾莎  范佩爾探員
Teresa. Agent Van Pelt.
什么風把你們吹來了
What brings you two here?
你為什么沒有告訴我們
Why didn't you tell us
就在弗羅斯特殺害帕克曼之前一周
you called Frost
你給他打過電話
the week before he killed Parkman?
聽我說  這事兒沒什么值得懷疑的
Look, there's nothing suspicious about it.
天眼組織雇我是為了
I was hired by Visualize
保護帕克曼不受弗羅斯特的傷害
to protect Parkman from Frost.
那你可真稱職啊
Bang-up job.
弗羅斯特威脅說
Frost was threatening
要對我們非法解約提起訴訟
a wrongful termination suit.
我以為他只是想要錢
I figured he was just looking for a payout.
你是怎么跟他說的
What'd you say to him?
我告訴他
Well, I told him that
帕克曼身后有天眼組織的律師團
Visualize's lawyers were behind Parkman,
他們會將訴訟一直耗下去
and they'd keep it in the courts,
直到弗羅斯特傾家蕩產
until Frost had spent his last penny.
怎么了  雷
What's wrong, Ray?
這些問題讓你不自在了嗎
These questions making you uncomfortable?
你看到了嗎  就在那兒
Do you see that? It's that.
蜘蛛
It's a spider.
我討厭蜘蛛
I hate spiders.
現在好些了嗎
Better now?
聽我說
Look. It...
我從來沒想到過
It never occurred to me that Frost was
弗羅斯特會計劃進行一起謀殺
planning anything like a murder.
我從來就不覺得他會是很暴力的那種人
He didn't really strike me as the violent type.
只能說又長見識了吧
Live and learn, I guess. Hmm.
吃一塹  長一智
Sometimes you get it wrong. Next time you do better.
我想搞清弗羅斯特是怎么逃走的
I've been trying to figure out how Frost got away.
就是簡還沒弄明白的所謂把戲
You know, the trick that Jane can't figure out.
然后呢
And?
我們都知道當時還有第三人在場
Well, we know there was a third man.
是的  就是殺了弗羅斯特的人
Yeah, the one who killed Frost.
當時現場應該還有第四個人
There had to be a fourth as well.
-一個做內線的男人  -做內線的男人
- An inside man. - An inside man?
也可能是女人
Or woman.
服務員  廚師  行李員  任何人
A maid, a cook, a bellboy, whatever.
一個能夠幫助弗羅斯特在酒店進出自如
Somebody who could help Frost get in and out of the hotel
而不會被發現的人
without being seen.
沒有證據表明弗羅斯特和任何酒店員工有聯系
There's no evidence Frost had contact with any of the hotel's employees.
我們都問過話了
We did interviews.
那又怎樣  可能有人撒謊了
So? Somebody lied to you.
在酒店保安到達房間之前
The killer could have already been gone
兇手可能就已經逃走了
by the time hotel security got to the room.
所有的現場目擊者都說他們聽到
All the witnesses said they heard a struggle
房間里有打斗的聲音
going on inside the room.
聽到的和看到的可以大相徑庭
Uh, there is a difference between hearing and seeing.
尸檢報告出來了
Autopsy report just came out.
帕克曼被刀刺中后并未立即死亡
Parkman wasn't immediately killed from the knife wound.
被刺傷后他又掙扎了一段時間
He died from a struggle sometime after being stabbed.
他死于主動脈大出血
He had an aortal hemorrhage.
所以  不用謝
So... you're welcome.
你是怎么在我們之前拿到尸檢報告的
How did you get the autopsy before us?
特蕾莎  我在加調局還是有些朋友的
I still have friends in CBI, Teresa.
有求必應的那種
They help when I need it.
說到幫助朋友
Speaking of... helping friends,
能給你們倆一點建議吧
a word of advice for both of you.
是嗎  什么建議
Yeah? What's that?
簡
Jane.
他把事情搞得一團糟
He's made a mess of things.
他不懂得適可而止
He doesn't know when to leave well enough alone.
你知道我的意思吧
You know what I mean?
不  我不知道
No, I don't.
他已經得罪了很多有權有勢的人物
There's a lot of powerful people that Jane's pissed off,
不僅僅是血腥約翰
not just Red John.
你們倆最好在有些事發生之前
You should get out of the way, both of you,
先躲遠點
before something happens.
我真的不愿意看到你們受到傷害
I really--I'd hate to see you get hurt.
這話從你嘴里出來還真是有趣  雷
It's funny you should say that, Ray,
因為事實上關于帕克曼謀殺案
because, actually, we're putting your name
你也在我們的嫌疑人名單里
on a list of suspects for Parkman's murder.
什么  你們瘋了嗎
What? That's crazy.
弗羅斯特和帕克曼可能都是
The third man could have killed
被那個第三人所殺
both Frost and Parkman.
是弗羅斯特殺了帕克曼
Frost killed Parkman.
也許這正是那個第三人
Maybe the third man just
希望我們認為的
wanted it to look that way.
也許就是你  雷
Maybe it's you, ray.
也許你就是那個第三人
Maybe you're the third man.
你有殺人動機
You have motive.
我只希望你們記住一點
I just hope you remember this.
我盡力幫忙了
That I tried to help.
好嗎
Okay?
我要看那份尸檢報告
I want to see that autopsy report.
多謝前來  科德羅警探
Thanks for coming in, Detective Cordero.
真的非常感謝
I really appreciate it.
不用謝  叫我奧斯卡吧
Yeah. Call me Oscar.
環境真不錯
Nice digs you got here.
你們加調局沒有精簡預算這么一說吧
No expense spared for you CBI folks, huh?
喝點什么  咖啡行嗎
Yeah. Can I get you something? Coffee?
不用了  謝謝
Nah, I'm fine.
這是柯克蘭被擊斃案的文件
Here's the file on the Kirkland shooting.
里面有獄方的報告和我的調查報告
It's got the prison report plus my investigation.
有什么值得注意的嗎
Anything that stuck out?
沒有
Nah.
我覺得就是一個變態小子不能忍受坐牢
Only a sick puppy who couldn't hack doing his time,
想方設法想逃出去
looking for any way out... in my opinion.
你跟擊斃他的獄警談過了嗎
And you spoke to the correctional officer who shot him?
當然
Oh, yeah.
他還是個毛頭小子
He was just a kid.
說柯克蘭只顧著跑
Says your guy Kirkland paid no attention
完全無視三次口頭警告
to three verbal warnings, just kept going,
甚至連頭都沒有回一下
didn't even turn around.
那孩子只好開槍了
Kid had to shoot.
你知道  這種人最招人恨了
You hate to see someone like that, you know?
總是有人渣
Some piece of crap
逼得一個警察做出自己
making a cop do what he ain't
最不想做的事
got the stones to do himself.
這不公平
It ain't right.
還有
And I'll tell you something.
那孩子被這事搞得一團糟
Messed the kid up really bad.
創傷后應激障礙之類的
P.T.S.D... or something.
太令人遺憾了
It's a damn shame.
我能留一份復印件嗎
Can I make a copy of this?
沒必要
Don't need to.
想著你們可能用得著  已經印好給你了
Brought that one for you. Thought you might want it.
謝了
Thanks.
別客氣
Hey, no problem.
也許哪天你也能幫我什么忙  是吧
Maybe one day you'll do a favor for me, right?
事情都搞清楚了
He clear things up?
說不上  他倒是說都一清二楚了
Not really. I mean, he says it was clean.
柯克蘭想逃跑  本來沒人想打死他
Kirkland was trying to escape, nobody wanted to shoot him,
不過他們沒辦法  不得已動手了
but they were forced to-- reluctantly.
-你不相信  -這上面說
- You don't buy it. - Well, it says in here
他背部中了六槍
he was shot six times in the back.
開了六槍可不像是不得已才動的手
Six doesn't sound so reluctant.
就是啊
No, it doesn't.
不過也只能得到這套說辭了
That's the story we're gonna get.
好吧  我去告訴頭兒
Okay. I'll tell the boss.
周金寶在嗎
Uh, where can I find Kimball Cho?
那是他的位子  不過他暫時不在
That's his desk, but he stepped out for a moment.
有什么事嗎
Can I help you?
算有吧  我今天早上在體操館碰到他的
Maybe. I met him this morning at the gym.
我想過來看看能不能請他
I thought I'd come by and see if he wants to let me
喝杯咖啡
buy him a cup of coffee.
開車過來的路上還覺得想法挺正常的
Plan seemed normal when I was driving over here,
怎么現在感覺自己像跟蹤狂一樣
but now it's feeling a little stalker-ish.
你有這種感覺嗎
Does it seem stalker-ish to you?
有一點兒吧
A little. Yeah.
好吧  我還是走吧
Okay, I should go.
記得我嗎
Remember me?
-認識  體操館那位  -對
- From the gym, yeah. - Yeah.
-過來  坐會兒  -該死的腳脖子
- Come here. Sit down for a second. - Darn ankle.
謝謝
Thanks.
你來有什么事
What are you doing here?
我叫基拉  基拉·汀斯利
My name's Kira. Kira Tinsley.
我本來想請你喝杯咖啡
I was gonna buy you a coffee,
不過不太好  我還是走吧
but it was a bad idea. I'm gonna go.
別走  喝杯咖啡沒關系的  稍等
No, I can drink a cup of coffee. Give me a second.
帕克曼一開始被刺傷
Uh, when Parkman was stabbed,
匕首只是劃過肋骨
the knife glanced over the rib
只是輕微劃傷了主動脈
and barely nicked the aorta.
哈弗內沒瞎說  法醫說
Haffner wasn't lying. And the coroner says that
帕克曼遇刺后還經歷了一番打斗
there was a struggle after the stabbing
導致傷口撕裂
that caused the nick to tear, and that's what started
所以才大出血而死
the hemorrhaging that killed Parkman.
如果弗羅斯特和帕克曼真打斗過
And if Frost and Parkman were really struggling
而且因此引起帕克曼大出血
and that's what caused the hemorrhage,
那弗羅斯特身上怎么沒有濺滿帕克曼的血
how is it that Frost didn't get Parkman's blood all over him?
而且他離開酒店房間的時候
And how did he avoid tracking bloody footprints
怎么會沒有留下血腳印
out of the room?
簡
Jane?
我破案了
I just solved the case.
是嗎  怎么做到的
Really? How?
-真的  不過先去辦件事  -簡
- Yeah. But one thing first. - Jane?
格蕾斯
Grace?
周剛剛見的那個女的是誰
Who was that woman Cho just met with?
叫基拉·汀斯利吧
Someone named Kira Tinsley.
-就是他在體操館認識的那個女的  -對
- Oh, the woman he met at the gym? - That's right.
挺漂亮的  是吧
Attractive, right?
還好吧  如果你喜歡那一型的話
She was okay, if you like that type.
-格蕾斯  你去過體操館嗎  -當然
- You, uh, you ever go to the gym, Grace? - Sure.
你會在那兒物色男朋友嗎
You ever try to pick up a guy there?
不會
Ugh. No.
他們有沒有說去哪兒了
Uh, did they happen to say where they were going?
喝咖啡去了吧
Coffee.
話沒說完你就一走了之了
Now you just walk out in the middle of a conversation?
-里斯本  能請你幫個忙嗎  -怎么
- Lisbon, can I ask a favor? - What?
能不能找一根那種彈力訓練帶
Can you go get one of those elastic exercise bands,
就是那種幫助人伸展的帶子
the kind to help you stretch with?
你要那東西干嘛
What do you need one of those for?
把它帶去帕克曼住的酒店房間
Bring it to Parkman's hotel room.
我們那兒見
I'll meet you there.
我的職業嗎
What do I do?
負責客戶關系的  挺無聊的
Oh... client relations. Boring stuff.
跟我說說加調局的事吧
Tell me more about the CBI.
就是份工作  幫助人們
It's a job. Uh, we try to help people,
抓住壞人
try to stop the bad guys.
-你不擅長聊天吧  -是啊
- You don't talk much, do you? - No.
沒關系
It's all right.
-我就喜歡這樣的男人  -太好了
- I like that in a man. - Good.
周
Hey, Cho.
你是基拉·汀斯利吧
Kira Tinsley, right?
是啊
Yeah.
這是你的嗎  看上去挺好吃的  能吃嗎
Is that yours? That looks good. May I?
什么
What? Oh.
這蛋糕好吃
Nice muffin.
我想這是你的吧
I think this is yours.
這是什么
What is that?
從沒見過
I've never seen one of those.
是竊聽器  用來竊聽的設備
It's a bug. A listening device.
是嗎  我是在金寶的桌子下面找到的
Really? Because I found that under Kimball's desk
我敢肯定是你的
and I was certain that it belonged to you.
-何出此言  -因為它
- Why would you say that? - Because it goes with, uh...
和這個一套的  看
this. Here.
這是你的錢包
And here's your wallet,
上面說你是私家偵探
and that identifies you as a private investigator,
是吧
doesn't it?
對  好吧  行了
Yeah. All right. Okay.
我就不該接這個活兒  不過
That's why I don't take jobs like this, but...
那個客戶預先付了錢  所以
the client paid cash up front, so...
給我吧
I'll take this.
-不行  不能給你  -什么
- No, you can't-- you can't have those. - What?
你不能
You can't--
糟糕
Oops.
那可花了我三百塊錢呢
That cost me 300 bucks.
是吧  真抱歉
Yeah, I'm sorry.
失陪一會兒
Excuse me a minute.
等等
Hey! Wait a minute.
我只是拿錢做事
Look, it was just business.
不是針對你的  行了嗎
Nothing personal, okay?
你的客戶是誰
Your client--who was it?
你知道我不能說
You know I can't reveal that.
行  根據加州刑法第632條  你被捕了
All right, I'm arresting you under section 632.
加州刑法第632條規定了關于違法竊聽的刑罰手段
夠你在牢里呆上一年的
That's worth a year in jail.
等等  別這樣
Hey, wait a second! No, whoa, whoa, whoa!
有事好商量
We can work something out here, right?
天吶  你想知道什么
Jeez. What do you want to know?
那人雇你做什么
What were you hired to do?
竊聽你們的辦公室  接近你
Bug your office, get close to you.
客戶想掌握你們的一切動態
Client wanted to know everything you and your team knew.
你的客戶是誰  是天眼組織嗎
And who was your client? Was it Visualize?
是的
Yeah.
沒事了吧
So are we good?
你是天眼組織成員嗎
Are you Visualize?
不是
No.
誰付我錢  我就給誰賣力
I just work for whoever hires me.
行了嗎
Are we done?
行了
Yeah, we're done.
我覺得你挺好的
Look, you seem like a nice guy.
我們和好吧
No hard feelings?
她好像受雇于天眼組織
Looks like she was hired by Visualize.
我叫人盯著她
I'm gonna put a tail on her.
不用
No need.
我在她包里放了竊聽器
I put the bug in her bag.
隨時竊聽她就行了
We can listen to her whenever we like.
我們去解開那宗雙重謀殺案吧
Let's go solve that double murder, shall we?
好吧
Right.
特蕾莎
Teresa.
知道我們來這兒干嘛嗎
Any idea why we're here?
你的簡先生叫我們來的
Your Mr. Jane asked us to come.
你是要教我們跳健身操嗎
Oh--are you gonna teach us aerobics?
簡一會兒就到
Jane will be here any minute.
槍是在這附近找到的  對嗎
So the gun was found somewhere here, right?
然后酒店在
And the hotel is...
那邊  對吧
that way, yes?
對  這樣看不見
Right. You can't see it,
就在墻的那一面
but it's just the other side of that wall.
-我猜對了  -什么猜對了
- I'm right. - About what?
你和瑞斯比待在這兒  保持高度警惕
Uh, you stay here with Rigsby, and keep very alert.
我可不想有人受傷
I don't want anyone getting hurt.
終于來了  我們在這兒等很久了
Oh. Finally. We've been waiting here long enough.
好飯不怕晚
All good things come to those who wait.
你要用伸展帶破這個案子
You gonna solve the case now with a stretchy band?
對  這是其一
Yes, among other things.
首先請重點注意
The first thing that's important to note
帕克曼和弗羅斯特是情侶
is that Parkman and Frost were lovers.
同性戀
Gay?
-不  他們不是  -他們是的
- No, they weren't. - Yes, they were.
沒聽說過這事
We never heard anything about that.
因為帕克曼還是弗羅斯特的教練時
No. Because the relationship started
他們就已經在一起了
when Parkman was Frost's coach.
當時弗羅斯特還未成年
When Frost was still a minor.
我從來不必擔心
And I never felt I had to worry
她和教練單獨在一起
about him being alone with her.
我說過  弗羅斯特少年時
Like I said, Parkman was Frost's mentor
帕克曼就是他的導師了
since he was a teenager.
一直到現在嗎
And continued to the present day?
是的  后來他們的戀情不順
Yes. Then the relationship started going badly.
帕克曼去歐洲時  他們終于決裂了
When Parkman went to Europe, that was the final straw.
麥勒認為弗羅斯特趁帕克曼不注意
Mylar thought Frost was sneaking away
開溜了
when Parkman wasn't looking.
帕克曼去參加歐洲的體操錦標賽了
Parkman went to a gymnastics tournament in Europe.
以前  弗羅斯特都會跟他一起去的
In the past, Frost went with him.
這一次他沒去
This time, he didn't.
帕克曼沒有邀請弗羅斯特  所以弗羅斯特想歪了
He had it backwards. Parkman hadn't invited Frost.
他認為帕克曼有了更年輕的新情人
So he assumed that he was being replaced
取代了他的位置
with a younger lover...
于是決定報復
And decided to seek revenge.
他想提出非法解約的控告
So he tried filing a wrongful termination suit,
卻受到了天眼組織的恐嚇
but he found himself being intimidated by Visualize.
在帕克曼去酒店
So he tried the hard touch,
出席會議時  他決定硬碰硬
when Parkman came to the hotel for the conference.
他們的戀情一直是兩廂情愿
Now their relationship had always been a consensual one,
但在公眾眼中和法律之下
but that wouldn't matter in the eyes of the public
卻沒什么差別
or the law.
只要弗羅斯特一句話
It was in Frost's power to transform Parkman
帕克曼可能就會從奧林匹克教練
from a--an Olympic coach to a child molester
淪為兒童猥褻犯
with just a few words.
他讓帕克曼用牛皮紙裝一大筆錢
He demanded that Parkman bring a large sum of money
穿過公園過去見他
across the park in a brown paper bag.
否則他就會毀掉帕克曼的生活
Or Frost would ruin Parkman's life forever.
弗羅斯特猜對了
And Frost was right in his estimation
帕克曼一定會破財消災
of what Parkman stood to lose.
卻沒想到他會作何反應
What he didn't realize was how Parkman would react.
汽水瓶消音器非常有用
The soda bottle silencer worked perfectly.
就算爆掉了  也沒人聽見
Even if it did blow off, no one heard a thing.
但帕克曼沒想到
But, uh, Parkman hadn't expected
弗羅斯特會帶刀
that Frost would have a knife.
傷口看起來不大
The wound looked to be minor,
帕克曼把槍放回包里
so Parkman put his gun back in his bag
沒管弗羅斯特
and he left Frost.
但帕克曼已經慌了神
Already Parkman was starting to panic.
車里發生的事沒按他計劃的進行
What happened in the car hadn't gone to plan.
一切都亂了套
Nothing was going to plan.
你這人怎么回事
Whoa! What the heck?!
你到的時候  帕克曼正在想辦法
And when you arrived, Parkman was trying to figure out
處理兇槍
what to do with the gun.
窗戶是他唯一的機會
The window was his only chance.
但他不能就這樣把槍扔出去
He couldn't just throw it out there, though.
那樣只能扔到外面這條街上去
It would end up right down there in the street.
但是  如果他能
But... if he could just
帕克曼先生
Mr. Parkman.
把槍
Get it...
扔遠一點
a little... further.
就
Just that little...
遠
bit...
一點點
further.
搞什么
What the hell?
槍墜到小巷地面上時  走火了
When the gun landed on the ground in the alley, it went off.
這就是證人聽到的槍響
That was the gunshot that witnesses heard.
電視遙控器
TV remote.
我們應該能在小巷的某處
Very likely we'll find a bullet hole
找到彈孔
somewhere in the alley.
那誰殺了帕克曼  那些血哪來的
But who killed Parkman? Where'd all the blood come from?
帕克曼拉松緊帶時
Uh, when Parkman pulled on the elastic...
他的主動脈破裂了
His aorta--it ruptured.
高能預警
Fore!
搞什么
What the hell?
救命
Help.
他捅了我
He stabbed me.
你是說根本沒人出入過這間房
So you're telling me that nobody came in or out of the room.
一直只有帕克曼先生一個人嗎
It was just Mr. Parkman the whole time?
是的
Yeah.
巧妙之處就在于毫無玄機
The trick was that there was no trick.
就這樣
Et voilà?
再見  里斯本探員  簡先生
Good-bye, Agent Lisbon, Mr. Jane.
恕我直言  我可不希望
I hope you won't be insulted when I say
再見到你們了
that I hope I won't be seeing you again.
沒事
Oh, we won't be.
哈弗內先生在這兒的話一定會謝謝你們的
I'm sure Mr. Haffner would say thank you if he were here.
他在哪呢  不聽聽最后帶刺的褒獎就走
Where is he? It's not like him to leave
可不是他的風格
without one last barbed compliment.
他還有些事要處理
Oh, he had some business to attend to.
我不是他唯一的客戶
I am not his only client.
但愿你們的辦公室很私密
I was hoping your office could be discreet.
你們明白我意思的
You know what I mean.
明白
Yes.
說到
Uh, speaking...
私密
of discreet,
竊聽加調局可不是什么好主意
It was stupid of you to try and bug the CBI.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
雇個天眼組織以外的人
Hiring someone outside Visualize
也許讓你自以為很安全
might have made you feel safe,
但她已經承認是你雇的她
but she admitted that you hired her.
周探員告訴我的
Agent Cho told me.
不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我只能說  就算有人竊聽你們
But all I can say is that if someone did bug you,
那也肯定不是我
it wasn't me.
再見  里斯本探員
Good-bye, Agent Lisbon.
簡  你沒事吧
Jane? Are you okay?
得讓格蕾斯馬上追蹤這個
Grace needs to trace this immediately.
怎么了  出什么事了
Why? What's going on?
庫伯沒撒謊  他沒竊聽加調局
Cooper wasn't lying. He didn't bug the CBI.
那是誰
Well, who did?
血腥約翰  我們得找到基拉·汀斯利
Red John. We need to find Kira Tinsley.
她要么跟血腥約翰是一伙的
She either works for Red John,
要么馬上就要成為他下一個目標了
or she's about to become his next victim.
她在城北那邊  頭兒
She's in the north section of the city, boss.
范佩爾正在查地址
Van Pelt's working on the address.
-手機不接  固話正忙  -我們知道
- No answer on her cell, and the landline's busy. - Yeah, we know.
你們說九點到六點
Yeah, you say 9:00 to 6:00,
卻根本沒人來
and then you never even show up.
就快查到了
Almost got it.
不行  我付錢讓鐘點工在家待了整天
No. I paid my cleaning lady to stay here all day
好給那人開門  但他壓根沒來
to let the guy in, and then he never came.
好了
Okay.
櫟臺街1065號
1065 Oak Terrace.
我們在道格拉斯街  往福爾松街方向
We're on Douglas, headed toward Folsom.
不  今晚就給我來修有線電視
Yeah. No, I want my cable fixed now, tonight,
不然我就
or I'm gonna--
我就...等一下  有人來了
I'm g--yeah, hold on a second. Somebody's here.
請薩城警局盡快派人趕去櫟臺街1065號
I need Sac P.D. to 1065 Oak Terrace fast as they can.
好了  來了
Okay, I'm coming!
好了  還有十來分鐘車程  我們會給你指路
Okay, you're about ten minutes away. We'll direct you.
能開快點嗎
Could you drive faster?
頭兒  下一個路口左轉
Boss, you're gonna want to take the next left...
在埃爾卡米諾街右轉
and then a right on El Camino.
有輛巡邏車就在六個街區之外
Got a patrol car six blocks away.
警察  我進來了
Police! I'm coming in!
薩城警察到了
Sac P.D.'s on scene.
加油  振作點
Come on. Oh, come on, stay with me.
振作點  你會沒事的
Stay with me. You're gonna be okay.
加油  振作點
Come on, stay with me.
埃爾卡米諾街右轉  頭兒
Right on El Camino, boss.
該死
Damn it.
開就是了  里斯本
Just drive, Lisbon.
急需救護人員
I need E.M.T.s.
請立即提供醫療援助
I need medical assistance immediately.
看著我  沒事的  好嗎
Now look at me. You're gonna be fine, okay?
他們正趕來了  等...
They're on their way. Wait--
急救人員在哪  我們需要急救人員
Where are the E.M.T.s? We need E.M.T.s.
我是加調局的  誰干的
I'm CBI. Who did this to you?
告訴我
Tell me.
紋身
Tattoo...
他左手臂上有紋身
Tattoo on his left arm.
她說什么了
What did she say?
她說血腥約翰左肩膀有個紋身
She told me Red John has a tattoo on his left shoulder.
三個點
Three dots.
這是我的籌碼
That's my leverage.
逮住他了
I got him.